<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>EJam's Space</title><link>https://ejammy.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on EJam's Space</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 22:02:28 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ejammy.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Package Managers: Getting Softwares on Linux (and MacOS / Windows)</title><link>https://ejammy.github.io/posts/package-managers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 22:02:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ejammy.github.io/posts/package-managers/</guid><description>A week ago I was installing homebrew on my friend&amp;rsquo;s computer and she had no idea what I was doing (not that I actually know what I&amp;rsquo;m doing), so I think it&amp;rsquo;s a good time to write a guide.
A package manager or package-management system is a collection of software tools that automates the process of installing, upgrading, configuring, and removing computer programs for a computer in a consistent manner.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://ejammy.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 21:19:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ejammy.github.io/about/</guid><description>A jar of jam with an e. I know how to type letters and symbols to make computer do stuff.
TODO Add chat system (Disqus?) Try out other themes Make my own theme What I&amp;rsquo;m working on Setting up Linux desktop with manjaro, neovim, and maybe a tiling window manager Skill tree More like messing around pretending to know stuff
Games Starcraft II Zerg gold Rainbow six siege Not even ranked Valorant iron?</description></item><item><title>Hello World (again?)</title><link>https://ejammy.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 01:29:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ejammy.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>Hello!
Blogging / Website / Portfolio What is this place? I have no idea, but take a look!
Some Ideas:
Write tutorials Take notes Personal wiki Showoff Testing int main() { return 0; } Math Some equations: $$ \sum_{i=0}^ni=\frac{n*(n+1)}2 $$
Title Subtitle headings headings headings headings strike through aaa bbb
frperg zrffntr&amp;hellip; pbatengf!
aa
aaa
About my last blog It was a mess.</description></item></channel></rss>